One of the myths bordering One Punch Man has been whether or
not our beloved sassy lost child wears undies or not.
For years, there have been rumors that she doesn't wear panties.
And this has been a topic of fierce discussion for
the One Punch Man fandom on whether Tatsumaki wear one or not.
Well, this is because there are several shorts like this one, this one, this one,
and this one where it is actually visible that Tatsumaki don't wear any.
But then on the chapter 181 of One Punch Man,
where Tatsumaki squares off with Saitama, it has been shown right here in a chibi
version that Tatsumaki actually wears panties.
Wait, are those panties or diapers?
And of course, the only man who can see her at such an awkward situation without
getting twisted to death has to be the strongest man alive in the name of King,
as expected of King whose power knows no bounds.